Nguyễn Khắc Ngọc Khôi

Front-End Developer

€ 0384111265 ► khoi.nkn12@gmail.com Ø linkedin.com/in/khoinkn12 • Dong Nai

CAREER OBJECTIVES

I am an experienced front-end developer with over one year of industry experience, demonstrating the ability to create intuitive user interfaces. Familiar with front-end development concepts, I am a goal-driven individual seeking opportunities to work in a professional environment and expand my knowledge and skills. I aspire to transition into a full-stack developer role.

EDUCATION

VNUHCM - University of Information Technology (UIT)

Sep 2015 - Jun 2021

Computer Engineering (embedded and robotics)

GPA: 2.76/4 (6.9/10)Graduation thesis: 9.3/10

WORK EXPERIENCE

ProtonX Sep 2022 - Apr 2024

Front-End Developer

Developed an education website to help users create and manage their content and students more efficiently. This website utilizes the MERN stack:

- Designed and improved the user interface for a website that allows teachers to create and manage classes and necessary teaching materials.
- Developed a user-friendly interface for students with features that support the learning process.
- Implemented automated email tools and integrated AI for content creation.
- Designed APIs for CRUD tasks using Express is and MongoDB.
- Developed an advertising website for courses using Next.js, optimizing it for SEO.
- Deployed the website on Cloudflare.

Technologies used: React.js, Bootstrap, Redux, Next.js, Node.js, Express.js, MongoDB.

The University of Information Technology

Jun 2019 - Mar 2021

Research Assistant

Researched basic and modern neural network architectures, focusing on sensitive object detection using the YOLO model. Technologies used: Python, Tensorflow, YOLO.

SKILLS

- Linux
- Git
- React.js
- Node.js
- Express.js
- MongoDB

CERTIFICATIONS

TOEIC 510 2020 - 2022